Okay, buckle up, because the
universe is secretly hilarious and
also possibly lying to us.
Did you know, botanically speaking,
a banana is actually a
berry, but a strawberry isn't?
Mind blown!
My whole fruit salad
identity is a lie!
Speed speed should be 5x.
Record scratch.
And get this, Oxford University
is older than the Aztec
Empire.
Like, buy a lot.
Chimes.
So next time you're complaining
about ancient textbooks, just remember,
they've been there since before Cortez.
Probably still using the same Wi-Fi.
Speed speed should be 5x.
Oh, and here's a fun one.
It rains diamonds on Jupiter and Saturn.
Diamonds!
Sparkle sound.
Meanwhile, I'm just here paying rent.
What gives, cosmos?
Playful grumble.
Makes you wonder what else
they're not telling us, right?
Mystery music fades out.